BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.8616: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., San Antonio Chapter and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 14, 1961-1965 (Box 37, Folder 8616)
  - Code no.8618: Dallas County Construction Employers Association and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1960- 1973 (Box 37, Folder 8618)
  - Code no.8619: Associated General Contractors, Inc., Houston Chapter and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Locals 213, 1334, 973, 1890, 3201, 1962-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8619)
  - Code no.8620: Building Contractors Association of Indianapolis and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1962- 1972 (Box 37, Folder 8620)
  - Code no.8621: General Contracting Business and Carpenters District Council of Jacksonville and Vicinity, 1962-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8621)
  - Code no.8622: Builders' Association of Kansas City and UBC Kansas City and Vicinity, 1961-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8622)
  - Code no.8623: Associated Building Contractors of Northwestern Ohio, Inc. and Maumee Valley Carpenters District Locals 248, 1138, 1581, 1393, 1960-1972 (Box 37, Folder 8623)
  - Code no.8626: Allied Construction Employers Association and Carpenters District Council of Milwaukee County and Vicinity, 1960- 1968 (Box 37, Folder 8626)
  - Code no.8655: Associated General Contractors of America, Detroit Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 324, 324A, 324B, 324C, 1960-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8655)
- Series IV: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.204: Patrick Cudahy, Inc. and United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Code no.206: Food Industry, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Locals 81, 151, 186, 329, 529, 554, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Code no.209: Independent Packing Houses of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 195, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Code no.212: Oscar Mayer and Company, Inc. and Beef Boners and Sausage Makers Local 100, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Code no. 215: Meat Trade institute, Inc. and Butcher's Union of Greater New York and New Jersey, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Code no.226: Associated Milk Dealers and Milk Drivers Union Local 753, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Code no.227: Associated Milk Dealers of Denver and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Local 537, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Code no.228: Dairy Industrial Relations Association and IBT Locals 93, 166, 186, 306, 441, 572, 683, 871, 898, 952, 982, 1961- 1964 (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Code no.229: Good Humor Corporation and IBT Local 443, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Code no.231: Thompson Dairy and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Local 246 of Washington, D.C., 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Code no.232: Wholesale Dairy Industry and Milk Wagon Drivers' and Creamery Workers' Union Local 380, 1959-1972 (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Code no.256: Campbell Soup Company and RWDSU Local 194, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 256)
  - Code no.251: California Packing Corporation and RWDSU Local 17, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - Code no.258: Eugene Fruit Growers' Association and Cannery Workhouse Men, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers Local 656, 1962- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 258)
  - Code no.259: H.J. Heinz Company and Canning and Pickle Workers Union Local 325, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 259)
  - Code no.267: General Foods Corporation and United Cereal, Bakery and Food Workers Local 374, 1960-1971 (Box 2, Folder 267)
  - Code no.270: Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers Local 3, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 270)
  - Code no.272: A.E. Staley Manufacturing Co. and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 837, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 272)
  - Code no.273: Clinton Corn Processing Company and American Federation of Grain Millers Local 6, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 273)
  - Code no.274: Chicago Bakery Employees' Labor Council and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union Local 1, 1960- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 274)
  - Code no.276: Employers of Metropolitan Area of Washington, D.C. and Bakers Local Union Local 118, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 276)
  - Code no.278: Wholesale Division of Essex, Hudson, Monmouth, Passaic and Mercer Counties and Bakery Drivers and Salesmen, AFL, 1955- 1960 (Box 2, Folder 278)
  - Code no.283: New York City Bakery Employers Labor Council and Bakery Drivers Union Local 550, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 283)
  - Code no.289: Wholesale Bakers Group and Bakery Drivers Local Union 276, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 289)
  - Code no.291: American Crystal Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, 1959-1965 (Box 2, Folder 291)
  - Code no.301: Utah-Idaho Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers Locals 281, 268, 276, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 301)
  - Code no.304: Planters Nut and Chocolate Company and Department Store Union Local 26, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 304)
  - Code no.315: Breweries of Detroit, Michigan and Brewery Workers' Locals 3, 38, 181, 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 315)
  - Code no.321: Joseph E. Seagram and Sons, Inc. and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union Locals, 7, 10, 13, 16, 34, 52, 109, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 321)
  - Code no.322: Hiram Walker and Sons, Inc. and Distillery Workers' Union Local 55, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 322)
  - Code no.323: Winery Employers Association and Distillery Workers Union Local 45, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 323)
  - Code no.328: Great Western Sugar Company and Teamsters, Warehousemen and Sugar Workers Union, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 328)
  - Code no.330: Carnation Company and Central Conference of Teamsters Union, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 330)
  - Code no.331: Minneapolis Milk Dealers and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Union Local 471, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 331)
  - Code no.334: Borden's Farm Products of New Jersey, Inc. and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Union Local 680, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 334)
  - Code no.337: Greater Cincinnati Milk and Ice Cream Dealers Association and Milk and Ice Cream Drivers and Dairy Employees, 1959- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 337)
  - Code no.338: Dried Fruit Processors of California and National Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Local 11, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 338)
  - Code no.342: Ice Cream Council, Inc. and Ice Cream and Frozen Custard Industry Employees Local 717, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 342)
  - Code no.345: Chock Full O' Nuts Corporation and UMW, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 345)
  - Code no.348: California Bakery Employers Association and IBT, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 348)
  - Code no.350: Nestle Company and P.C.K. Employees Union, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 350)
  - Code no.355: Metropolitan Milk Industry and IBT Local 338, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 355)
  - Code no.361: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union Local 484, 1966- 1968 (Box 2, Folder 361)
  - Code no.500: American Tobacco Company and Tobacco Workers' International Union Local 247, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 500)
  - Code no.502: American Tobacco Company and Tobacco Workers' International Unions 182, 183, 181, 192, 204, 216, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 502)
  - Code no.504: Liggett and Myers Tobacco Co. and Tobacco Workers' International Union Locals 176- 177, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 504)
  - Code no.505: P. Lorillard Company and Tobacco Workers International Union Local 201, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 505)
  - Code no.506: P. Lorillard Company and Tobacco Workers International Union Local 317, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 506)
  - Code no.510: DWG Cigar Corporation and Cigar Makers Local 209, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 510)
  - Code no.511: Jno. H. Swisher and Son, Inc. and Cigar Makers International Union Locals 86, 119, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 511)
  - Code no.512: Brown and Williamson Tobacco Corporation and Tobacco Workers International Workers Local 187, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 512)
  - Code no.601: Crown Cotton Mills and TWUA, 1959-1971 (Box 3, Folder 601)
  - Code no.603: Erwin Mills, Inc. and United Textile Workers of America, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 603)
  - Code no. 604: Erwin Mills, Inc. and United Textil Workers of America, Local 257, AFL-CIO, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 604)
  - Code no.608: Bates Manufacturing Company and TWUA, 1956-1962 (Box 3, Folder 608)
  - Code no.612: Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. and TWUA, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 612)
  - Code no.614: Pacific Mills and TWUA, 1952-1968 (Box 3, Folder 614)
  - Code no.619: Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers Association and Knit Goods Workers Union Local 190, 1955-1966 (Box 3, Folder 619)
  - Code no.620: Munsingwear, Inc. and TWUA Local 66, 1958-1965 (Box 3, Folder 620)
  - Code no.622: Plain Dye and Machine Print Companies and TWUA, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 622)
  - Code no.631: Beaunit Fibers and United Textile Workers of America Local 201, 1955-1964 (Box 3, Folder 631)
  - Code no.800: Clothing Manufacturers Association of America and ACWA, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 800)
  - Code no.803: Arrow Company and ACWA, 1953-1969 (Box 3, Folder 803)
  - Code no.804: Cotton Garment and Allied Industries and Philadelphia Joint Board, ACWA, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 804)
  - Code no.806: Manhattan Shirt Company and ACWA, 1953-1966 (Box 3, Folder 806)
  - Code no.812: Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. and ILGWU, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 812)
  - Code no.813: Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis and ILGWU, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 813)
  - Code no.814: California Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc. and ILGWU Local 994, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 814)
  - Code no.815: California Sportswear and Dress Association, Inc. and ILGWU Local 994, 1957-1970 (Box 3, Folder 815)
  - Code no.819: Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers' Association and ILGWU Locals 55, 84, 97, 512, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 819)
  - Code no.821: Coat and Suit Group of Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. and ILGWU, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 821)
  - Code no.822: Bobbie Brooks, Inc. and ILGWU Cleveland Joint Board, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 822)
  - Code no.824: New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc. and ILGWU, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 824)
  - Code no.825: Kenrose Mfg. Company, Inc. and ILGWU, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 825)
  - Code no.826: National Association of Blouse Manufacturers and ILGWU Local 10, 1959-1970 (Box 4, Folder 826)
  - Code no.827: National Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc. and ILGWU Dressmakers' Joint Council, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 827)
  - Code no.860: Uniform Manufacturers Exchange and ILGWU Local 66, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 860)
  - Code no.861: Schiffli Lace and Embroidery Manufacturers Assoc. and United Textile Workers of America Local 211, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 861)
  - Code no.865: Boston Apparel Guild and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt and Dressmakers Union Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, 80, 1961- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 865)
  - Code no.866: Merit Clothing Company, Inc. and ACWA Local 607, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 866)
  - Code no.869: Levi Strauss Co. and ACWA Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1962-1971 (Box 4, Folder 869)
  - Code no. 871: Association of Rain Apparel Contractors and Waterproof Garment Workers Union, Local 20; Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 871)
  - Code no.873: United Underwear Contractors' Association, Inc. and Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union Locals 10, 62, 1963- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 873)
  - Code no.875: Bayly Manufacturing Company and ACWA, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 875)
  - Code no.882: Men's Neckwear Association of New York, Inc. and ACWA New York Joint Board of Neckwear Workers ,Locals 250, 253, 1964- 1970 (Box 4, Folder 882)
  - Code no.1689: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and Ampthill Rayon Workers, Inc., 1960-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1689)
  - Code no.1913: Converse Rubber Corporation and Federal Labor Union 22763, 1958-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1913)
  - Code no.1914: B.F. Goodrich Footwear Company and Rubber Workers' Union Local 21914, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1914)
  - Code no.1915: Servus Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 215, 1961- 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1915)
  - Code no.1916: American Biltrite Rubber Co., Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 156, 1958- 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1916)
  - Code no.1928: Bristol Manufacturing Corporation and United Rubber Workers of America Local 220, 1962-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1928)
  - Code no.2102: Associated Shoe Industries of Southeastern Massachusetts, Inc. and Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1961- 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2102)
  - Code no.2104: Brown Shoe Company and United Shoe Workers of America Local 245, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2104)
  - Code no.2105: Brown Shoe Company and Boot and Shoe Workers Union Local 778, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2105)
  - Code no.2108: Shoe Manufacturing Companies, Massachusetts and United Shoe Workers of America Local 245, 1960-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2108)
  - Code no.2113: Slipper and Play Shoe Industry Employers and United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council 13, 1954-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2113)
  - Code no.2115: Samuels Shoe Company and Boot and Shoe Workers Union, 1959-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2115)
  - Code no.2116: Weyenberg Shoe Manufacturing Company and Boot and Shoe Worker's Local 170, 651, 721, 663, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2116)
  - Code no.2123: Acme Boot Company, Inc. and United Rubber Workers, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2123)
  - Code no.6305: Meat and Poultry Purveyors Association, Inc. and Butcher's Union of Greater New York and New Jersey Local 174, 1961- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 6305)
  - Code no.203: Cudahy Packing Company and United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1959-1967 (Box 25, Folder 203)
  - Code no.218: Rath Packing Company and United Packing House, Food and Allied Workers Local 46, 1959-1970 (Box 25, Folder 218)
  - Code no.282: National Biscuit Company and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union Local 42, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Code no.4610: Covered Button Association of New York and ILGWU Local 66, 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4610)
- Series V: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.29: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and Badger Ordnance Works Council, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.1001: E.L. Bruce Co. and UBC Local 2846, 3124, 2523, 2825, 2639, 2509, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1001)
  - Code no.1004: Potlatch Forests, Inc. and International Woodworkers of America, 1959-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1004)
  - Code no.1005: Simpson Timber Company and Industrial Workers of America Local 3-38, 1959-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1005)
  - Code no.1009: Southern California Lumber Employers Council and UBC Local 2288, 1961-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1009)
  - Code no.1010: Woodwork Employers Association and UBC Local 2846, 3124, 2523, 2825, 2639, 2509, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1010)
  - Code no.1011: Woodworkers Association of Chicago and Carpenters District Council of Chicago, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1011)
  - Code no.1026: Masonite Corporation and International Woodworkers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1026)
  - Code no.1277: West Virginia Pulp and Paper and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Locals 134, 216, 217, 728, 780, 831, 998, 1967- 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1277)
  - Code no.1900: Armstrong Rubber Company and International Union of United States Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 93, 164, 303, 703, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1900)
  - Code no.1902: Dunlop Tire and Rubber Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 135, 1961- 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1902)
  - Code no.1904: General Motors Corporation, Inland Manufacturing Division and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers Local 87, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 1904)
  - Code no.1909: Lee Rubber and Tire Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers Local 227, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1909)
  - Code no.1911: Seiberling Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers Local 278, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1911)
  - Code no.1917: American Biltrite Rubber Co., Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 25, 1960- 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1917)
  - Code no.1920: Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc., Manhattan Rubber Division and Manhattan Rubber Workers Independent Union, Inc., 1961- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1920)
  - Code no.1921: Seamless Rubber Company and United Rubber Workers of America Local 338, 1957-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1921)
  - Code no.1922: Dryden Rubber Division and United Rubber Workers of America Local 108, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1922)
  - Code no.1929: Aeroquip Corporation and United Rubber Workers of America Local 102, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1929)
  - Code no.1931: Ohio Rubber Co. and United Rubber Workers of America Local 338, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 1931)
  - Code no.2322: Ideal Cement Company and United Cement Workers, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2322)
  - Code no.2338: Norton Company, Behr-Manning Division and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 17, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2338)
  - Code no.2343: Owens-Illinois, Inc., Toledo Libbey Products Plant and American Flint Glass Workers Union of North America Local 700, 1963- 1971 (Box 6, Folder 2343)
  - Code no.2344: Monolith Portland Cement Company and United Cement Workers Union Local 52, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2344)
  - Code no.2345: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation and International Brotherhood of Operative Potters Local 7, 1963- 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2345)
  - Code no.2353: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement Workers Union, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2353)
  - Code no.2354: General Portland Cement Company and United Cement Workers, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2354)
  - Code no.2366: Medusa Portland Cement Company and United Cement Workers, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2366)
  - Code no.4611: Armstrong Cork Company, Lancaster Floor Plant and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1961- 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4611)
  - Code no.6311: Oil, Petroleum, Chemicals and Liquid Products Employers and IBT Local 801, 1959-1970 (Box 23, Folder 6311)
  - Code no.1210: Gulf States Paper and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 297, 1959-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1210)
  - Code no. 1225: Oxford Paper Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 900, AFL-CIO, 1961-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1225)
  - Code no.1226: Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1963- 1967 (Box 25, Folder 1226)
  - Code no.1277: Westvaco and United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1277)
  - Code no.1603: Diamond Shamrock Chemical Co. and District 50, Allied and Technical Workers Local 12231, 1960-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1603)
  - Code no.1622: Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation and OCAW Local 7-267, 1961-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1622)
  - Code no.1669: Hercules Powder Company and International Association of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Forgers and Helpers of America Local 26, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1669)
  - Code no.1681: Procter and Gamble Company and Ivorydale and St. Bernard Employees' Representation Association, 1960- 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1681)
  - Code no.1688: Johnson and Johnson and TWUA, 1959-1970 (Box 26, Folder 1688)
  - Code no.1694: Max Factor and Company and Warehouse, Processing and Distribution Workers' Union Local 26, 1968-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1694)
  - Code no.1800: American Oil Company and OCAW Local 4-449, 1960-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1800)
  - Code no.1801: American Oil Company and Independent Petroleum Workers of America Local 1, 1962-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1801)
  - Code no.1802: Atlantic Refining Company and Atlantic Independent Union, 1950-1956 (Box 26, Folder 1802)
  - Code no.1803: Cities Service Refining Corporation and Lake Charles Metal Trades Council, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 1803)
  - Code no.1805: Humble Oil and Refining Co. and Operating, Mechanical and Maintenance Employees, 1958-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1805)
  - Code no.1806: Gulf Oil Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Local 4-23, 4-254, 1959-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1806)
  - Code no.1807: Esso Standard, Division of Humble Oil Company and Independent Industrial Workers' association, 1960-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1807)
  - Code no.1808: Humble Oil and Refining Co. and OCAW Local 4-333, 1961-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1808)
  - Code no.1809: Magnolia Petroleum Company and OCAW Locals 4-243, 4-229, 1958-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1809)
  - Code no.1810: Richfield Oil Corporation and OCAW, 1959-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1810)
  - Code no.1812: Shell Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Local 4-367, 1959-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1812)
  - Code no.1813: Shell Oil Company and OCAW, 1959-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1813)
  - Code no.1814: Atlantic Richfield Company and OCAW Local 4-23, 1959-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1814)
  - Code no.1815: Standard Gas Company and Independent Union of Petroleum Workers, Inc., 1958-1966 (Box 27, Folder 1815)
  - Code no.1815: Standard Pipe Line Company and Independent Union of Petroleum Workers, Inc., 1958-1966 (Box 27, Folder 1815)
  - Code no.1908: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1970- 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1908)
  - Code no.2301: Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2301)
  - Code no.2302: Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1959-1972 (Box 27, Folder 2302)
  - Code no.4418: General Aniline and Film Corporation and International Chemical Workers Union Local 306, 1960-1968 (Box 33, Folder 4418)
  - Code no.4426: Warminster Fiberglass Company and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4426)
- Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.4: Bendix Corporation and IAM Local 71, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.5: General Dynamics - Pomona and Engineers and Architects Association, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6: General Dynamics - Astronautics and Engineers and Architects Association, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.9: Lockheed Aircraft Corporation and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 727, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Code no.14: Ford Instrument Company and United Instrument Workers Local 425, 1956-1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.15: Ford Instrument Company and IUE, 1956-1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.16: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and IAM Lodge 609, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Code no.17: Remington Arms Company, Inc. and Employees' Mutual Association, 1956-1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.22: Chance Vought Aircraft and UAW Local 893, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.26: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and IBEW Local 1805, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.31: Philco-Ford Corporation, Aeronutronic Division and UAW Local 1430, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.35: Sperry Rand Corporation and IAM AFL-CIO Local 228, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.36: Federal Cartridge Corporation and IAM AFL-CIO Local 77, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Code no.38: Day and Zimmermann, Inc. and UBC Local 379, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.1102: Kroehler Mfg. Co. and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1102)
  - Code no.1103: Simmons Company and Upholsterers' International Union of North America Locals 63, 424, 422, 420, 173, 421, 1958- 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1103)
  - Code no.1107: Upholstery Employers Association and Upholsterers, Decorators and Allied Crafts Union Local 44, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 1107)